Guide to the Jack Censer collection, 1953-2011
George Mason University. Libraries. Special Collections Research Center.
- Series 4: Research, 1968-2006 (Boxes 27-42)
  - Glossy prints of 18th century French illustrations and a periodical, circa 1990s-2000s (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Photocopies of 1975 Keith Thomas article and "What is the Third Estate?,", circa 1980s-1990s (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Lecture flyers and maps of France and Europe, 1960s-1970s, 1989 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Scott, John Anthony, "Francois-Noel Babeuf and the Conspiration des Egaux,", circa 1960s (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Cornell University Special Collections research materials and notes (1 of 2), circa late 1980s (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Cornell University Special Collections research materials and notes (2 of 2), circa late 1980s (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Photocopies of "The Spectator,", circa 1980s-1990s (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Affiches de Paris (3), 1745-54 research material, circa 1980s-1990s (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Literature article (La press litteraire en 1789, Francois Souchet), circa late 1980s-1990s (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Photocopies of French 18th century pamphlets (labelled "not Prospectuses"), circa 1980s-1990s (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Lists, letters, and notes related to research on French 18th century periodicals, 1987, late 1980s (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Photocopies from French 18th century periodicals (labelled "prospectuses/research papers") and notes (1 of 2), circa late 1980s (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Photocopies from French 18th century periodicals (labelled "prospectuses/research papers") and notes (2 of 2), circa late 1980s (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Photocopies from French 18th century periodicals (labelled "unsorted prospectus"), circa late 1980s (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Photocopies of French 18th century periodicals, circa late 1980s (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Photocopies of French 18th century periodicals, A-B, circa late 1980s (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Photocopies of French 18th century periodicals, C, circa late 1980s (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Photocopies of French 18th century periodicals, D-E, circa late 1980s (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Photocopies of French 18th century periodicals, F, circa late 1980s (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Photocopies of French 18th century periodicals, GHI, circa late 1980s (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Photocopies of French 18th century periodicals, J, circa late 1980s (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Photocopies of French 18th century periodicals, KLMNO, circa late 1980s (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Photocopies of French 18th century periodicals, PQR, circa late 1980s (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Photocopies of French 18th century periodicals, S, circa late 1980s (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Notes and ideas, journalists ch(apter?), photocopies, circa late 1980s (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Literature chapter notes and photocopied articles, circa late 1980s (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Notes on book chapters (labelled "reflections"), circa late 1980s (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Notes on revising, circa late 1980s (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Notes from book on French 18th century periodicals (labelled misc. notes for Censer book), circa late 1980s (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Notes on Affices chapter, circa late 1980s (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Affiches de Paris (9), 1755-64 photocopies, circa late 1980s (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Annonces de Normandie (20) 1765-1774 photocopies, circa late 1980s (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Affiches de Paris (28) 1775-1786 photocopies, circa late 1980s (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Affiches de Poitou 28A 1775-1786, circa late 1980s (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Affiches de Bordeaux (50), 18th century, photocopy, circa late 1980s (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Notes from research on the 18th century French press, related material, 1990 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - "Imaging the French Revolution," "Depiction of the Revolutionary Crowd," online collaboration organized by Jack Censer and Lynn Hunt, 2004 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - "Imaging the French Revolution" text and images (1 of 2), 2002 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - "Imaging the French Revolution" text and images (2 of 2), 2002 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - "Imaging the past" essays and images, 2003 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - International Congress on the History of the French Revolution bicentennial of the Revolution conference planning, 1987-1989 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - International Congress on the History of the French Revolution bicentennial of the Revolution conference planning, 1988-1989 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - International Congress on the History of the French Revolution bicentennial of the Revolution reception planning, 1988 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - "Imaging the French Revolution" emails and captions, 2003 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - South African history volume, 1992 (Box 31, Folder 9)
    Restricted - SSN
  - Routledge publishing series correspondence, etc., Georgetown lecture, 1990-1993 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Book/series proposal correspondence, 1990-1995 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Rewriting the History of the Palestionan Question, prospectus and report, Ilan Pappe, 1996 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Routledge contract for "The French Press,", 1992 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Routledge publishing proposals, 1990s-2000s (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Wadsworth Publishing permissions, 1988-1989 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Barbara Melosh's "Gender and American History since 1890,", 1991-1992 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - "The Holocaust: Origins, Implementation, Aftermath," ed. Omer Bartov, 1995 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - David Crew book proposal and reactions, 1991 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Duara proposal email, 1999 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Cultural Approaches to Stalinism authors, 1998 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Jeffrey Wasserstrom, "The Chinese Revolution," correspondence on proposal, 1997-1998 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Melvyn Leffler, "The Origins of the Cold War" prospectus, 1993 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Karras/McNeil book prospectus and evaluations, 1991 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Lenard Berlanstein Industrial Revolution volume, 1991 (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - Bonnie Smith book correspondence, 1997 (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - The Revolutions of 1989 volume proposal and comments, 1995-1996 (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - Slavery, Capitalism and Culture, Bill Harris prospectus and comments, 1991 (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - "The French Press" book, Routledge, 1994 (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - Gary Kates French Revolution book proposal, 1995 (Box 32, Folder 19)
  - Phil Morgan book proposal and reviews, 1991-1992 (Box 32, Folder 20)
  - Margo Todd, "Reformation to Revolution" prospectus and reviews, 1992 (Box 32, Folder 21)
  - Routledge expenses, 1991 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Images for book on Fauquier County, 2006 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - "Fauquier at 250" sidebars, images, 2006 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - "Fauquier at 250" endnotes, 2006 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - "Fauquier at 250" comments, correspondence, 2006 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - "Fauquier at 250" introduction comments, contracts, correspondence, author information, 2004-2006 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Cinq Annees Literarires 1745-1754 (7) photocopies, circa 1980s (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Annales Typographiques, 1755-1764 photocopies (11), circa 1980s (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Courrier d'Avignon 1765-1774 (23) photocopies, circa 1980s (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Gazette de Leyde, corresponds to decade, researched but not used, circa 1980s (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - List of publications, chart, correspondence with archives, 1982 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Reader Literature, 1980s (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Journal economique, 1745-1754 (4) photocopies, circa 1980s (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Journal des Dames, 1764-1775 (18) photocopies, circa 1980s (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Gazette de France photocopies (25), circa 1980s (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Journal de Lecture, 1770-1775 (26) photocopies, circa 1980s (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Gazette Universelle de Litterature 1770-1775 (24A) photocopies, circa 1980s (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Gazette de France (8) photocopies, circa 1980s (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Courrier d'Avignon 1755-1765 (15) photocopies, circa 1980s (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Courrier d'Avignon 1745-1754 (5) photocopies, circa 1980s (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Gazette de France (16) photocopies, circa 1980s (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Gazette de France (1) photocopies, circa 1980s (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Courrier d'Avignon 1775-1786 (31 photocopies, circa 1980s (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Gazette de Bruxelles (13) photocopies, circa 1980s (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - La Nature Consideree (27A) photocopies, circa 1980s (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Botein, Ritvo, Censer Asecs and combined drafts I, circa 1980s (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Final Draft - Botein, Ritvo, Censer (1 of 2), 1981 (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Final Draft - Botein, Ritvo, Censer (2 of 2), 1981 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Olson/Martin book review by Jack Censer, 1996 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Harriet Ritvo and Steve Botein - notes - thinking - hypothesis, 1978-1981 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Information on manuscripts work, 1982 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence on Presse, 1977-1978 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Sample selection, circa late 1970s-1980s (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - "Bibliography, Press and Society in France 1715-1799,", 1970s-1980s (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Overview of thoughts and sample, circa 1970s-1980s (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Notes, correspondence, spreadsheet of publications for French Press work, 1970s-1982 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Tally sheets (counting) for French Press project, circa 1970s-1980s (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Tally sheet (counting) Ritvo and Botein French Press project, circa 1970s-1980s (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Working paper - Harriet Ritvo and Steve Botein, late 1970s (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Draft 2 (labelled Draft 3 - complete, notes, appendices), 1979 (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - Drafts of articles (labelled 300 Romantic history), lists of 18th century publications, 1979 (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - Notes for Bielefeld paper, circa 1980s-1990s (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - French and German language articles by other authors, 18th century photocopies, 1980s (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - Handwritten notes from French 18th century publications, 1970s-1980s (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Colloque de Karlstad, Suede conference packet, 1994 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Beltman/Corbis permissions, 2001 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Scala/Art resource permissions, 2001 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Rights permissions for Western Civilization class, 2001 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Biblitheque Nationale de France permissions, 2001 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Foto Marburg permissions, 2001 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Granger collection permissions, 2001 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Tenth International Conference on the Enlightenment, Dublin, Ireland, 1999 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Press and Society in France definition of project, circa 1970s (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Introduction to Politics in Press, circa 1970s-1980s (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Drafts of journalist paper, circa 1980s (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - "Eighteenth Century Journalism and its Recruits" drafts, "Journal des Dames,", circa 1980s (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - "Eighteenth Century Journalism and its Recruits" comments by Jim Turner, 1984 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - Review letters and revisions of French Press paper, 1983-1984 (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - Research on chapter on journalists, circa 1970s-1980s (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - "Eighteenth Century Journalism and its Recruits" drafts, circa 1980s (Box 36, Folder 17)
  - "English Politics in the Courier d'Avignon,", circa 1970s-1980s (Box 36, Folder 18)
  - Penn State reviews, 1998 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Keele University, "The Press and the Public Sphere in Europe and America 1740-1840" descriptions (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Routledge reviews (employee review removed), 1995-1997 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Editorial for "Rethinking History,", 1996 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Lyon meeting, 1997 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Notes (labelled Readings), 1997 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Markoff, John review by Jack Censer, 1996 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - "The Social Ideal in the Affiches,", undated (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Les Gazettes Europeennes et L'Information Politique de l'Ancien Regime international colloquium, Lyon, France, 1997 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - "The Life and After-Life of Jean-Paul Marat,", circa 1970s-1980s (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Off-prints of publications, 1997-1998 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Hunt, Lynn review by Jack Censer, 1992 (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Ramsey, Clay review by Jack Censer, 1992 (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - Allen manuscript review by Jack Censer, 1991 (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - Popkin, Jeremy review by Jack Censer, 1980 (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - Retat, Pierre review by Jack Censer, 1982 (Box 37, Folder 16)
  - Shaeper, Thomas review by Jack Censer, 1983 (Box 37, Folder 17)
  - Sedgwick, Alexander review by Jack Censer, circa 1978 (Box 37, Folder 18)
  - Sigaut, Francois review by Jack Censer, 1979 (Box 37, Folder 19)
  - AHA (American Historical Association?) papers, 1991 (Box 37, Folder 20)
  - New York University Colloquium, 1991 (Box 37, Folder 21)
  - German program, 1985 (Box 37, Folder 22)
  - Southwest Texas State symposium, 1989 (Box 37, Folder 23)
  - Hesse, Carla review by Jack Censer, 1990 (Box 37, Folder 24)
  - Lyceum Press review letter, 1988 (Box 37, Folder 25)
  - Versions of Billefeld paper, circa late 1980s (Box 37, Folder 26)
  - "Soundings" program correspondence, information, 1985 (Box 37, Folder 27)
  - "Soundings" program correspondence, 1986 (Box 37, Folder 28)
  - Australia seminar, 1980s (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Comparative studies in society and history, 1989 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Declaration of the Rights of Man and the Citizen essay, circa 1970s-1980s (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - The Historian's French Revolution, World and I, circa 1980s (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Talk to Independent School teachers, circa 1980s-1990s (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Postdoctoral memos, 1970s (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Prelude to Power Johns Hopkins University Press reviews, correspondence, 1975-1978 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Morlock, Laura, Jack Censer, Robert Crain, "Civic Elites in Eighty-Eight Cities,", circa 1970s (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Morlock, Laura, Jack Censer, Robert Crain, "Civic Elites,", 1976 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Slavin, Morris review by Jack Censer, 1985 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Politics on press, 1st draft, circa 1970s (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Research notes, circa 1980 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - "The Relaxation of Ideological Hostility," Soviet history paper, 1969 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - American Economic Aid Soviet history paper notes, 1969 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - "The Prudery of the Parisian Radicals,", 1975 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Notes on engravings, "Engravers, Engravings, and the French Revolution,", 1975 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - "Prelude to Power" abstract, 1976 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - "Radicalism and Ideology,", circa 1970s (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Banquet presentation text and CDs, International Revolutions, circa 1990s-2000s (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Sgard, Jean correspondence, research on French 18th century publication, 1982 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - "Three Newspapers of Paris,", 1971 (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Senior thesis - "Communist Tactics and Socialist Party Factionalism,", 1968 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - An analysis of the theoretical writings of Jerome Petion, 1969 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - "A Study of the Bastille, 1660 to 1665 and 1726 to 1737,", 1969 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence on Engraving paper, 1978 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Engravings paper, 1975 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Engravings paper, 1970s (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Final draft, engravings paper, circa 1970s (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Notes and pages of papers, circa 1970s (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - American Historical Association proposals and comments, 1977 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Western Society for French History, 1977 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - American Society for 18th Century Studies meeting, 1979-1980 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Journal of Social History article-reviews, 1987 (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - Western Society for French History conference, 1980-1982 (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - Western Society for French History conference, 1981 (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - Engravings from Desmoulins-photocopies, circa 1970s (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - First Draft on engravings, circa 1970s (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - Consortium on Revolutionary Europe paper, 1987 (Box 40, Folder 17)
  - Comment - Consortium on Revolutionary Europe, 1988 (Box 40, Folder 18)
  - Encyclopedia of Social History, 1991 (Box 40, Folder 19)
  - American Historical Association guidelines, circa 1990s (Box 40, Folder 20)
  - Dictionary of the French Revolution entries and correspondence, 1978-1983 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Entry on the Press for "Historical Dictionary of Napoleonic France," correspondence, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Danton and Babeuf biographies review, 1979 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - "The Press in Old Regime France," University of California Press, Princeton correspondence, forms, reviews, etc, 1984-1987 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - The Dorsey Press correspondence, 1987 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Koren prize committee, 1981-1984 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Southern Historical Association metting papers and correspondence, 1976 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Maza review by Jack Censer, 1992 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - European and American intellectual history series, 1984 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Western Civilization textbook review, 1986 (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - University of Pittsburgh review, 1987 (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Pretence-Hall volume review, 1987 (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - Review for "The Historian,", 1986 (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - University of North Carolina Press review of Bailey Stone, 1979 (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - Temple University Press review of Mary Johnson, 1978 (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - "The Eighteenth Century: Theory and Interpretation" review of George Armstrong Kelly, 1978 (Box 41, Folder 16)
  - Review of George Armstrong Kelly for Princeton University Press, 1979 (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Article on V.O. Key from Southern Politics Conference (SAUS II), circa 1977 (Box 41, Folder 18)
  - American Historical Association, 1979-1980 (Box 41, Folder 19)
  - Consortium on Revolutionary Europe, 1981 (Box 41, Folder 20)
  - Western Society for French History paper, 1983 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - American Historical Association, 1984 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - American Historical Association papers, 1989 (Box 42, Folder 3)
- Series 5: Administrative papers, 1972-2011 (Boxes 42-44)
  This series contains material from 1972-2011 that documents Censer's work as Chair of the Art and Art History department at George Mason University. Also included are materials for work he did beyond the university for the Educational Testing Service and Bryant Adult Center, as well as correspondence and graduation programs from other institutions.
  - Certificate and awards program for ten years of service to George Mason University, 1988 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, contact information for various colleagues, 1976-1988 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Evaluations for review as chair of the History/Art History department, 2005 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Students - record of a meeting with Paul Schilling, 1999 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Resignation letter from College of Charleston, 1977 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Materials for review, 1995-1996 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Plans for Alternative General Education folder, Honors 240 syllabi and paper/exam questions, 1997 (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Johns Hopkins University Press catalog, Johns Hopkins commencement programs, 1972-1976 (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - Grant materials, 1976-1977 (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - New York Times article on George Mason University at 29, 1986 (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - Graduation program from Duke, other pamphlets, 1968-1970s (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Homebook inventory with photos, circa 1970s-1980s (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Lists of films/non-book media on the French Revolution and Napoleon, 1987, circa 1989 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Fullbright application, 1984 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Grants, 1985-1987 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - College of Arts and Sciences History department self-evaluation, 1996 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Cornell Summer Session letter, 1995 (Box 43, Folder 7)
    W4 removed
  - General education requirements, 1995 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Adult learning materials, 1995 (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Faculty committee requests, 1996 (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - Washington Area French Historians Group, circa 1990s (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - George Mason salary equity study and response, 1996 (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - General Education Committee, 1994 (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - Educational Testing Service (ETS), 1996 (Box 43, Folder 14)
  - Faculty Rewards and Incentives Committee, 2002 (Box 43, Folder 15)
  - Incheon Free Economic Zone (IFEZ), Mason Korea (Songdo), Ras-Al-Kaimah, 2006-2010 (Box 44, Folder 1)
    Restricted until 2025
  - Islamic Studies Center at George Mason University, 2011 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Faculty Rewards and Incentives Committee meeting materials, circa 2000s (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Grants, 1982-1983 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Memo from Marion Deshmukh on chairing the history department, 1995 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Governor's School for the Gifted at George Mason University, 1981-1982 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Faculty Rewards and Incentives Committee articles, memos, tenure-related research, etc. (1 of 2), 2000-2002 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Faculty Rewards and Incentives Committee articles, memos, tenure-related research, etc. (2 of 2), 2000-2002 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Western Society for French History administration, 1979-1983 (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Change' magazine, 1992 (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Educational Testing Service - questions submitted for AP European History exam, 1977 (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - University of North Carolina - Wilmington history master's program consultation, 1986 (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Certificate from Bryant Adult Center, 1993 (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - Memo to the George Mason University History department, December 3, 1982 (Box 44, Folder 14)
- Series 6: Audiovisual materials, 2001-circa 2010s (Box 45)
  This series dates from 2001 to circa 2010s and largely contains CDs of D.C. Sniper-related research materials and copies of Microsoft Word, Eudora, and Outbox files. There is also an interview on two audiocassettes.
  - Jack Censer documents zipped, CD, circa 2000s-2010s (Box 45)
  - Jack Censer documents unzipped, CD, circa 2000s-2010s (Box 45)
  - WJLA Int., CD, circa 2000s-2010s (Box 45)
  - PDFs of ads for 'Fight for Fairfax,' CD, circa 2000s-2010s (Box 45)
  - Folders C-E DSS, CD, July 4, 2004 (Box 45)
  - Interviews - Sniper, CD, November 2004 (Box 45)
  - Sniper/Press research project interview files transfer disk, circa mid-2000s (Box 45)
  - Folders A-B DSS, CD, July 4, 2004 (Box 45)
  - ShadowTV #1 CNN - October 3, October 14, October 15, October 19, October 20, CD, circa mid-2000s (Box 45)
  - ShadowTV #2 October 7 - WUSA, WRC, WJLA, Fox, October 11 - Fox, WRC, WUSA, CD, circa mid-2000s (Box 45)
  - ShadowTV #3 - October 22 WRC, October 11 WUSA, October 21 CNN, October 15 CNN (0030-0035 only), CD, circa mid-2000s (Box 45)
  - ShadowTV #4 WTTG (Fox) October 22, WUSA October 22, WJLA October 22, CD, circa mid-2000s (Box 45)
  - ShadowTV #5 WTTG (Fox) October 24, WRC October 24, WUSA October 23, WJLA October 24, CD, circa mid-2000s (Box 45)
  - WUSA 24th 8 files, CD, circa mid-2000s (Box 45)
  - Sniper map image files, CD, circa mid-2000s (Box 45)
  - Outstanding Coverage of a Continuing Story - Sniper Trials - WTOP News Team, CD, circa mid-2000s (Box 45)
  - WTOP October 16, CD, circa mid-2000s (Box 45)
  - Collage WTOP, CD, circa mid-2000s (Box 45)
  - History Channel French Revolution preview, CD, circa 2000s-2010s (Box 45)
  - Blank CD, circa 2000s-2010s (Box 45)
  - The Press meets the Washington Sniper, Jack R. Censer, CD, 2009 (Box 45)
  - AHR Correspondence, Projects Eudora, CD, circa 2000s-2010s (Box 45)
  - Eudora mail, CD, May 3, 2005 (Box 45)
  - Jack's Eudora, CD, December 21, 2001 (Box 45)